[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "What can you tell us about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, it seems that the French aircraft that spotted this Libyan aircraft, and as far as we know the type of aircraft that's a trainer aircraft used for training pilots who are going to move on to fighter jets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Misrata"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "And Nic, I mean, do you get a sense of the no-fly zone is actually having much of an impact on Gadhafi and his regime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "It seems to be having an impact around Misrata.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "I mean, on the ground, militarily and politically, what difference does it really make?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, I think it is the transition that the president talked about where our role diminishes somewhat, we're still very central in the planning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean, just looking at the way this has all been playing out, it seems to me that America is heavily involved but doesn't really want anyone to know that which seems to be a rather pointless exercise in terms of the PR here, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, no someone is pretending that America is not involved.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "And dare I say it, leadership here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, I have to disagree with you there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "So why should you be overly concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, we're concerned, and we are involved to stop a massacre.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Are they in this or not really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, I think, first of all, our -- the objectives militarily have been clear from the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Does America then re-enter the fray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "First of all, I don't think we're withdrawing leadership on the diplomatic, on the political stage.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Where does this policy have consistency?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, I think it has consistency in the sense that we see throughout the region that people are demanding both greater participation in their political life and also greater economic opportunities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Is it really America's job to get involved in civil wars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "OSNER: It's America's job to lead on human rights and democracy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$100", "$150 million"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "$", "CD", "TO", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "John, is that an accurate assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "You know, what it eventually will bring could easily be $100 to $150 million.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "And some of the jewels were actually from the duchess of Windsor's collection, weren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Windsor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "And that makes her, John, I would imagine, one of the great private jewelry collectors of all time, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Without question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Was she Hollywood's queen in all senses including the tiaras and bangles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Absolutely, I think Elizabeth Taylor of the maximum of glamour in the world right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Krupp"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "And John Block, what would be -- from your knowledge of the collection, the single most valuable piece that she owned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "You know, it's hard to say, but perhaps the Krupp diamond which was -- she was almost never -- not wearing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Block"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Don't you think, if I put you on the spot, do you think she preferred her diamonds to her men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "RINCE DIMITRI: Well, I think they went together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Windsor"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "And, John, if I could turn to you, I mean, did Elizabeth Taylor ever buy jewelry herself, or was it always just given to her by admiring men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "The only time she told me she ever bought jewelry for herself was at the Duchess of Windsor sale.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John", "Elizabeth Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "How would -- how would you imagine that she would like to be remembered knowing her as you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I didn't know her that well, but I think she liked to be remembered for her charitable works, for the -- for her totally generous personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "PRP$", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "And, Prince Dimitri, what would your memory of her be just from being a fan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "From being a fan -- from what I heard from lots of people who knew her is that she was an incredibly kind person.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dimitri"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March 11"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "What exactly is going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Piers, we have been getting aftershocks every single day since the March 11 earthquake and tsunami.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Do we know what their condition is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "We understand they're in a stable condition.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What's the latest advice there from the Health Ministry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "This is a very big story at the moment here in Japan because contamination is spreading.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Health Ministry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "And Jules, did you speak to her much about life in Japan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jules"], "LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "And Jean, when did you get the terrible news that confirmed that she had died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "About 5:20 on Monday morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Did it ever cross your mind that something awful could happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Oh, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What can you tell me about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "How would you like people to remember your daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Oh, she was loving and fun filled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RBR", "VBN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What was going through your mind as you ran towards her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "The only real things that I had going on in my mind were making sure that anyone who was injured, not just the congresswoman, but anyone who had been just in the immediate area got some treatment, and using whatever limited skills I had until someone who was better trained could come in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "What did you actually do to Gabby Giffords?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "So, the congresswoman as well as others had been shot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabby Giffords"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Did you fear in that moment that she was probably going to die, given the injury she'd sustained?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Did she say anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "She was conscious, but she wasn't able to speak.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Giffords"]}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Can you quite believe that she is where she is now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I think for people that don't know Congresswoman Giffords, it -- it's stupendous the amount of recovery that she's been able to make in such a short amount of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "How do you feel about being called a hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Still something that I'm not very comfortable with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Are you against marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "No, I'm for marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110324pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Do you think you will get married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]